CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name : Domitila Munyiva Matheka

Date of Birth : 14th December 1964

Gender : Female **Marital Status** : Married

Religion : Christian

Address : Box 26894-00100, Nairobi

Cell Phone Number: +254721748301

Email Address :mathekadm@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Long experienced Kenyan teacher who has worked in various government institutions as a teacher as well as a principal of such institutions overseeing that persons living with disabilities (PLWD'S) attain skills and knowledge for self- sustainability.

Am currently the chairperson of Butterfly care centre Africa on the community level, and advocating for the rights and privileges of PLWD'S as well as imparting knowledge and skills for self sustainability .

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

YEAR	INSTITUTION	AWARD
2010-2013	KENYA METHODIST	BACHELOR IN SPECIAL NEEDS EDUCATION
	UNIVERSITY	AND COUNSELING.
2003-2005	KENYA INSTITUTE OF SPECIAL	DIPLOMA IN SPECIAL NEEDS EDUCATION
	EDUCATION	
1982 -1984	KISII TEACHERS COLLEGE	P1 CERTIFICATE IN TEACHING
1977-1980	GATEGI SECONDARY SCHOOL	KCSE CERTIFICATE
1976	KARABA PRIMARY SCHOOL	KCPE CERTIFICATE

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 TO DATE: CHAIRPERSON BUTTERFLY CARE CENTRE AFRICA

POSITION HELD: CHAIRPERSON

2012-2016: PRINCIPAL JACARANDA SPECIAL SCHOOL

2006-2012: SPECIAL NEEDS TEACHER AT JACARANDA SPECIAL

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Working for the community
Helping the needy
Reading

REFEREES

1. MARION KIKONDE

CEO BUTTERFLY CENTRE AFRICA
P.O BOX 26894-00100

TEL:0712433559

marion.kikonde@gmail.com

2. FATHER VICTOR MAINA CATHOLIC PARIS EMBAKASI